He had a call with crypto bru we
Tuvo una llamada con crypto bru
were talking about various issues
estuvimos hablando de varios temas
regarding the complaint that has been filed against
acerca de la denuncia que le han puesto
Dallas It seems that they have enough
a Dallas Parece ser que tienen bastantes
evidence that Dallas resided in Spain
pruebas de que Dallas residía en España
between the years 2020 and 2024 there are ways
entre los años 2020 y 2024 hay maneras
to prove that Dallas has been in
de demostrar que Dallas Lleva años en
Santa Susana for years all this has already been
Santa Susana todo esto ya se le ha
passed to the Treasury but it is part of what was
pasado a Hacienda pero es parte de lo
passed to the Treasury about how he created
que se le pasó a Hacienda de cómo creó
the currency and so on at what point do you
la moneda y demás en qué momento te
start passing the Treasury something that does
pones a pasarle la hacienda una cosa que
n't even concern you and you make a
ni va contigo y le haces un archivo
Treasury file on another youtuber with whom
Hacienda sobre otro youtuber con el que
you are fighting investigate just you I
te estás peleando investigá olo tú Yo me
find apartments like this
encuentro con pisos como como Este vale
okay looked at that staircase okay now I'll
mirados esa escalera vale que ahora ya
warn you because no matter how much lizy or a
aviso porque por mucho que lizy oa se
put look look I have found out that this
pongan mira mira he averiguado que está
slab of the staircase I don't know what And it
losa de la escalera no sé qué Y es que
turns out that you in Estonia you can
resulta que tú en Estonia te puedes
create a company without any kind of
crear una empresa sin ningún tipo de
problem you Imagine the face of the
problema tú Imagínate la cara del de
Treasury when a doc arrives and it
Hacienda cuando le llegue un doc y
turns out that it is this youtuber who is
resulta ser que es este youtuber que se
fighting with another youtuber and  He has
está peleando con otro youtuber y le ha
done this research and it reaches the
hecho esta investigación y le llega al
other YouTuber and he says no, no, I have
otro youtuber y dice no no yo que tengo
tax residency in this country, yes. If
la residencia fiscal en este país sí Si
you can have tax residency in
tú puedes tener la residencia fiscal en
Andorra and as long as you do 180 days there,
andorra y con que hagas allí 180 días
wherever you are in the challenge, it doesn't matter.
donde tú estés en el reto da igual